<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unconscious Bias Talk And Wits Galway Launch April 2016 on Lynda O&#39;Leary</title>
    <link>http://lyndaoleary.com/tags/unconscious-bias-talk-and-wits-galway-launch-april-2016/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unconscious Bias Talk And Wits Galway Launch April 2016 on Lynda O&#39;Leary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://lyndaoleary.com/tags/unconscious-bias-talk-and-wits-galway-launch-april-2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Unconscious Bias talk and WITS Galway Launch-April 2016</title>
      <link>http://lyndaoleary.com/posts/2016-04-witsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyndaoleary.com/posts/2016-04-witsl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://lyndaoleary.com/img/WITS_launch_3.jpg&#34; style=&#34;display: block; margin: 0 auto;&#34;&gt;
On the 27th April, the WITS Galway group was launched.  The event took place at the Blackstone LaunchPad NUIG.
Women In Technology Science (WITS) is an independent, voluntary organization set up in 1990 to actively promote and support women in science, technology, engineering and maths (STEM).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mary Carroll was the main speaker at the event. Mary is the Vice-Chair of WITS and is a business strategist with over 25 years experience in design engineering, management consulting and business development. Mary gave an overview of WITS and followed with the Unconscious Bias workshop. The Unconscious Bias workshop covered:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;li&gt;What is unconscious bias?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examples of unconscious bias in the workplace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effects of unconscious bias&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Addressing unconscious bias&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The informative workshop sparked interesting questions and a diverse conversation between the participants. For more information about WITS Ireland, see: &lt;a href=&#34;www.witsireland.com&#34;&gt;WITS Ireland&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For information about Blackstone LaunchPad, see: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nuigalway.ie/blackstonelaunchpad/&#34;&gt;Blackstone LaunchPad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A special thank you to co-organiser &lt;i&gt;Dr Sandra Riordan&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Mary Carty&lt;/i&gt; Blackstone LaunchPad, and &lt;i&gt;Mary Carroll&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>